Aleksander Fret

tel.: 605 768 401

e-mail: aleksander.fret@op.pl www: aleksander.fret.com.pl

GitHub: www.github.com/alemikolo

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aleksander-fret



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Front-End Developer Creating web applications using modern technologies, like JS ES6,

React, Redux, Webpack, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB...

some experience with PHP and MySQL,

designing user interfaces (big experience in fhe field of graphics,

interest in UI UX).

Graphic Designer andCartographer Extensive editorial practice - designing of publications, DTP,

broad qualifications in the field of graphics software,

Big experience in making various maps.

EXPERIENCE

Sandstream Development 01/2019–now: position Software Developer.

Personal website 09/2018: www.aleksander.fret.com.pl – my online CV. Main

technologies: ES6, React, SASS, PHP.

11/2017-08/2018 (student): www.pixel-art-maker.fret.com.pl, Udacity

www.memorygame.fret.com.pl, www.arcadegame.fret.com.pl,

www.amusementparks.fret.com.pl.

10/2008-01/2019: Cartographer - Map Editor. Duties: designing Eko-Graf of graphic layouts and covers, editorial and cartographic tasks,

DTP, creating of advertising materials, preparing for printing.

10/2016: www.wilmat.com.pl. WilMat

Personal websites 07/2015: www.psychoterapia.fret.com.pl.

01/2015: www.ewa.fret.com.pl.

11/2012: Via Mercatorum, website, logo, advertising leaflet... Others

04/2007-07/2008: SeaStar, Cartographer,

11/2005–12/2006: Nowa Era, Author: Statistical tables, 09/2004-03/2005: Wydawnictwo Marek Rożak, Cartographer.

EDUCATION

11.2017–08.2018: Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree Udacity

Program (scholarship from Google).

Certain courses and trainings

React 16 - the complete guide; The Complete Sass & SCSS Course; PHP - developing CMS; PHP, MySQL, JS.

University of Wroclaw

10.1999-07.2005: bachelor's degree in Geography, master's degree in Geography, specialization in Cartography.

QUALIFICATIONS

Programming

JS ES6, OOP, React, Redux, Node.is, Express.is. MongoDB, Mongoose, JOuery, SASS, CSS, HTML, RWD, accessibility, Webpack, Gulp, Git, SEO, PHP, MySQL, Twig.

Graphics software

CorelDRAW, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Photo-Paint.

Others

English language (b1), Global Mapper.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Award in the competition organized by Ministry of Transport and Construction for master thesis Atlas regionalny województwa łódzkiego.

III prize for "[...] modern editorial style, usability [...]", Wrocław – przewodnik (J. Czerwiński, Eko-Graf), XX Ogólnopolski Przegląd Książki Krajoznawczo-Turystycznej. Scope of work: graphic design and creation, DTP.

PERSONAL TRAITS

Creative, with attention to detail, reliable, responsible. strongly involved.

INTERESTS

Playing the guitar, listening to the music, board games, fantasy literature, games and films, football, mountain hiking, listening to the Trojka radio channel.